tattooforaweek.com 2016-11-09

# Privacy & Cookies Fake Tattoos and Temporary Tattoos (Temporary tattoo) - TattooForAWeek, The Largest Online Temporary Tattoo Shop

**Privacy Policy**

WebManiac is committed to your privacy. Although most information on this site is available without personal data being transmitted, it is possible that the user's personal information is requested. This information will only be used within custom management and to keep you informed of our activities. The user can, free of charge and on request, always oppose the use of personal information for direct marketing. To this end he will turn to WebManiac BVBA, Pontstraat 9, 9031 Drongen, Belgium, [info@TattooForAWeek.com](mailto:info@TattooForAWeek.com).

Your personal details _ **are never passed or sold**_ to third parties.

According to the Law of 08/12/1992, the user has a legal right of access to or correction of personal data. Subject to proof of identity (copy of identity card) you can use a written, signed and dated request to WebManiac, Pontstraat 9, 9031 Drongen, Belgium, [info@Tattooforaweek.com](mailto:info@Tattooforaweek.com) to recieive a free written notice of your personal details. If necessary, you can also ask for a correction of incorrect, incomplete or irrelevant details.

WebManiac can collect anonymous or aggregated data of non-personal nature, such as browser type or IP address, operating system you use or the domain name of the website through which you have come to our website, or when you leave. This allows us to continuously optimize our site for users.

 **The use of cookies**.

During a visit to the site, cookies may be added on the hard drive of your computer and this only to make the site more responsive to the needs of returning visitors. These small files or cookies are not used to monitor surfing habits to other Web sites. Your Internet browser allows you to prevent the use of cookies, to receive a warning when a cookie is installed or to remove the cookies from your hard disk. Please consult the help function of your browser

Click [here](https://www.tattooforaweek.com/en/info/Cookies.html) for more information on cookies at TattooForAWeek.com.
